boy i got my mind on cake
all right guys um this video is going to
be about
how we can get ourselves stopped getting
wicked out i have a very
interesting thing that you can do it's
not
even uh stop placement related it's not
really
trading related it's not the actual
trade related it's a nice little trick
uh that you can use to your advantage to
help you
not getting stopped out uh and then we
will also talk about
the actual stop-loss placement and how
different methods you can use in order
to
get stopped out less often if it's going
to just wick you out
and then come back in the other
direction in the actual direction of
your favor
um so let's just talk about those
different things and then go enjoy our
cake
[Music]
so guys if you don't know already this
is the most woke trading community
in the world uh so hit that subscribe
button and you can join in
very very simple very free for you uh
and it helps me a lot um
in the growth of this channel um so i do
provide as much education as possible
and there is streaming available if you
guys want
to watch me live stream we can talk
about things answer your questions
uh you have because i am doing this out
of the comfort of my own home uh just
essentially for fun i like to teach on
youtube
and help you guys out as well um so this
is a game
of playing against the market makers
guys
they want you to lose money look at
these cats
walking all around me i have a cat on my
lap as well
so let's just keep talking while they do
their thing
so guys if you want to make that cake or
that dough
obtain the grain um you know however you
want to see it
uh you're going to have to work around
not getting manipulated by these market
makers
so the the very first thing you can do
is learn how to place your stops a
little bit easier
um and these are going to be methods
first of all you're going to have to be
looking for the manipulation
you're going to have to look for where
there is liquidity zones
i do have a video on how to spot
liquidity i will do more uh stuff on
liquidity
i talk a ton about liquidity and where
stop-loss placements are
in my live stream so please make sure
you check that out uh so you can learn
how to actually spot these uh stop
placements
you want to wait for other people to get
stopped out first of all
before you actually start entering
trades because then you're going to be
much less likely to become
that liquidity become that manipulation
that these banks are looking for in
order to fill
their orders this is a large portion of
how i am trading
now uh when we're diving into the actual
placement of the stop-loss let's give
you a little bit of technicals here
uh and jump into the chart let's just
say uh that you are looking at this
chart right here i will get rid of a
couple of these things
just so it's a little bit cleaner and
let's say that you did want to short
the euro going into this this is
actually a trade that i did
take today and there are different
methods that i just wanted to talk about
here and in how we're going to be
choosing where to place our stop loss so
in
an example like this normally what
you're going to be looking for is you're
obviously going to be looking for some
sort of area here
that you wanted to short on you want to
enter a trade somewhere around there
now first of all you have an option and
you can
just simply place a trade here kind of
blindly
and you can put a wider stop with some
room behind
and then you can put your target down
here now the problem with this
is you're going to avoid those stops but
you're not going to have a very sniper
entry are you you're going to have a
really wide stop
and you're not going to have a very good
risk reward ratio
so you can see how i was able to get a
much tighter trade
something around there um when i did
enter this trade because i am using
slightly different strategies here guys
so
first of all the thing you want to look
for is i did talk about wait for that
manipulation to happen
and then look for your entry right so in
this case we see the manipulation
actually happening here
right and then we see the reversal kind
of breaking down and then we would want
to get into that trade
now one of the things i do is when the
stop
is super super tight here you don't want
to be first of all just placing
a stop loss right behind that level
after you see the manipulation
you want to be giving it a little bit
more room if that's an incredibly tight
stop because this is something
that i would have actually gotten
stopped out on because it did manipulate
it
slightly again
so we gave this just a little bit more
room
and then it was super super close i
think i put it at 400 super super close
and because i have another method that
allows us to kind of
ignore some of the spreads which i will
tell you in a second so please make sure
you
keep watching guys um we actually
did not get stopped out and because
there was no spread on this trade
another situation is let's say uh you
are looking for this area now this area
here
um what you can do
is you want to wait for
that reversal to start right so let's
say you are waiting for the first
significant
uh down candle after you reach this zone
right
so this is your zone and
you want to see the first significant
down candle after you hit that zone so
we
see that zone doesn't really matter
exactly why we see this zone
but this is where we want short so now
we see a first down candle maybe this is
our reason
now instead of putting your stop behind
the previous level like i just talked
about there
where you'd be putting it up here it'd
be kind of a wider stop
what we can actually do is we can just
give this area a little bit of room
because most likely
after you see this confirmation that
we're actually break down here
we don't exactly need to put our stop
all the way back here
now this is not the best example uh what
would be a better example is if this was
much
further back if this was a longer wick
here so i'm just kind of explaining it
here as
an example that i saw today we don't
need it to be super super long but let's
say
it was all the way back here is where
that candle those candles kind of came
up to
it doesn't matter if it's a candle body
or a candle wick you're going to have a
wide stop and you don't want to be
putting it all the way back that way
so this is a method that we're going to
kind of be using
is that we see wait for that reversal
off that level and then again
you're going to give it a little bit of
room just in
within that same zone here and since it
does actually line up here quite evenly
in this case we would have just put it
here because why not
um because it's just a little bit a
little bit better uh or you put it
up here or whatever but if it is longer
there then um
you might want to just wait for that
reversal to happen and then put the stop
within the range
uh once you start seeing that reversal
hopefully that is something kind of
clear for you guys if you don't really
understand what i'm saying
jump into the streams and ask me some
questions there the thing that i did
want to talk about now
that is a fancy little trick here and it
has nothing to do with the actual charts
of
trading i mentioned there that i have a
method
that allows me to have no spread and
this is not
exactly true because the broker i use
still has spread and i still have to pay
those spread fees but something i've
done
is i actually created a demo account
on a broker that allows
for incredibly low spreads on the demo
accounts
and i'm not going to go into the brokers
i don't want to advertise the brokers
here on this video because it's not
point of this video
but you can find a broker with
incredibly low spreads and you can do it
on a demo account
and then what you can do is because
there is no spread on the demo pairs
but they mirror the actual live
pairs of a real account what you can
then do is you can set up a
a copy trader bot or something like this
uh you can set a
set up some sort of mirroring bot that
will mirror all of your trades directly
using the same account
percentage size and then you can have
multiple different accounts for
different purposes
mirroring different ways if this is
something that you'd like to do this is
personally what i do i have
four or five accounts for different
things and i mirror them all differently
uh and i have basically i only enter
trades on demo accounts
and then those demo accounts get
mirrored onto the live accounts and then
uh this uh spread doesn't actually apply
if the spreads do widen on the live
accounts at any point
then i don't get stopped out by that
spread change
i only get stopped out when the demo
account actually hits my stop loss
because it doesn't actually place any
trades
doesn't place any pending orders it only
basically reacts based off of the
actions of the demo account
so it's a amazing uh little
trick there that you guys
can use that's really going to save your
ass a couple times
from getting wicked out so hopefully if
you guys do like that little trick there
hit that like button
because that's something that i don't
think i've heard from anyone else before
and that was an idea that i came up with
and it's really
really helping me um if you guys want
any more information on how we can
actually
find these sniper trades i will be
releasing a video on
how we find sniper entries a little bit
more detail there
so that we can get a little bit more
precise a little bit better i will see
you guys next time
this is the most woke trading community
in the world uh and if you guys want to
follow me on instagram it's down there
it's in the description you know it's
always there just like every other
channel
you guys know it already hit the like
button see you guys next time
[Music]